This cake's great.
What a pitiful body.
Iorogi...
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... Silver Eyes.
It's Kobato!
Good morning, Kobato!
Good morning!
Kobato, can I put a ribbon on him?
Him? You mean Ioryogi?
Hey, gimme a break...
Yeah, go ahead!
It's so cute!
I'm sure he loves it!
Who the hell would love this?
Good morning.
Good morning, Kobato.
Let's do our best today.
Yeah!
I'm on my way, Ioryogi!
What's the doing carrying that around with her?
I'm sure it's important to her.
Yummy, yummy.
Cook, cook the baumkuchen, cook it, cook it.
The bears of the forest are cooking!
Oh, it's you.
Come on in, Ginsei.
He's not here.
I know.
So what did you come for?
There's something I want to know.
What's he up to?
Why ask me?
Whatever.
Even though we're like this now, we're from the spirit world.
Why are you bringing that--
Let's start from the beginning, shall we?
There's Heaven, the human world, the underworld, and the spirit world.
Humans are the only ones that don't know about the other worlds.
In Heaven, God rules over the angels.
In the underworld, the Devil rules over the demons.
And in the spirit world, the Spirit Lord rules over us.
Each of these worlds is unassailable in principle, but that damn fool Iorogi...
What? He's a fool.
We're like this because that idiot tried starting a war with Heaven, right?
There's gotta be something there he really wanted to make him do that, but...
But he didn't get it.
He should've just tried to filch it like that devil brat.
Anyway, because we lost and he shattered the inviolability of the worlds, he got turned into a stuffed animal.
I'm a baumkuchen-cooking bear.
And my Zuisho is a weird bird now.
Even God ran out of patience.
With all of us, but he was the ringleader.
So how does Iorogi get back to the spirit world?
Until that girl fulfills her wish, he's stuck in that body.
And he can't go back.
Her wish?
By healing humans' scarred hearts, and filling that bottle, her wish will be fulfilled.
Helping her is the deal he made with God.
I don't know what he's up to.
But I can tell you that ever since he came to the human world...
No, ever since he's been with that girl, he's been a little weird.
You should let him be for now.
Anyway, go ahead, have some.
Oh man.
It came out tasty, too.
Man, if my old buddies saw me like this, it'd bring a tear to their eyes!
Huh?
Over here, It!
Good morning, Kobato.
Domoto!
Why are you at the nursery?
I was looking for Kiyokazu.
Lunchtime, everyone!
Wash your hands and come inside!
Okay!
Kiyokazu.
What are you here for?
I figured you should come to lecture today, so I came to get you.
I can't go.
I thought you were looking forward to it.
Um... What's a lecture?
A lecture, at school.
It's something you do in college?
Yeah.
They've been taking attendance lately, huh.
You really should show up today.
Please go, Fujimoto.
I can't, I'm too busy.
Fujimoto!
Kobato!
It's okay, I have an idea.
That's enough. You have an important lecture this afternoon, don't you?
Sayaka...
I've helped out here plenty before.
That's when I realized.
We're having naptime today, and Kobato's helping out. It will be fine.
But...
Fujimoto.
You're always so helpful, but I want you to go to school too.
Please.
Okay...
Wow, he's so obedient.
Only to Miss Sayaka.
What the hell kind of fairy-tale getup is this!?
Later, Kobato.
I'll be back.
Come back soon!
Later!
See you!
I'll do Fujimoto's work too!
Wow, that's amazing!
Dammit! That bastard Fujimoto tied it on so tight I can't get it off!
Thanks for today.
I'm so glad you were here.
It's nothing!
Go home and get some rest.
Okay!
That ribbon suits little Ioryogi there.
Little... Ioryogi?
Sure. Anyway, see you tomorrow.
It's still a bit hot.
It'll probably be cooler on dirt rather than pavement.
This feels good.
Right, Ioryogi?
Oww!  Why'd you do that!
You're all tense right here!
You know why?
Because you're hungry?
Kobato...
The seasons are changing.
You didn't come here to help out at the nursery.
But Fujimoto wasn't there today, so I wanted to cover for him.
That's what I mean.
Do what you're here for!
If you don't hurry and fill this bottle up, your wish won't come true.
Ginsei?
A friend of yours?
Ioryogi!
So that's her.
Kobato!
Ioryogi...
Huh? That's...
If you break that, you're gonna regret it.
Why?
Why are you sticking around the human world in that body?
I've got something to do.
Ginko!
Zuisho! Quit making a ruckus inside!
You'll get feathers in the dough!
I can't help it, I'm a bird now.
I know, I know. Anyway, what is it?
I saw it! That selfish, violent guy that's a stuffed animal now and that other guy look like they're about to fight!
Oh.
What? That's all?
Fine, take this and give it to the loser as a consolation prize.
You mean we should let them do it? It looks like it'll get pretty ugly.
There's no stopping those two.
Ioryogi was the one who took him in.
He even named him.
Ginsei, after his silver eyes.
And it's still come to this.
I tried to hold them back, but I guess it's come down to this.
I see.
He's got a creepy fixation on Iorogi because of that.
They're the only ones that can settle it.
Give that bottle back!
Come and get it yourself, Ioryogi.
Feel like getting burnt?
You can't pin me down with that body.
You--
How pitiful.
Your body and your name. What's this "Ioryogi" thing?
Io... Ryo?
Iorogi!
Ioryogi!
Yeah, Iorogi!
Ioryogi?
Wrong, Ioryogi!
Huh?
Okay, Ioryogi!
I'm perfectly fine with what she calls me.
Now give me that bottle back!
Come back to the spirit world and ask me.
I told you, I've got something to do first!
I can't go back until I'm done.
It's about that "wish", right?
What does she mean to you, anyway!?
She's been pretty mean to me.
So why not get rid of her?
What!?
Without her, there'd be no wish to worry about.
You'd be able to return to the spirit world.
The old you would've done it.
Yeah, I guess.
She is pretty clumsy and dense.
I'll try my best!
She's always putting other people first.
Even though she's useless, she wrecks herself trying to help other people.
But I don't mind that kind of thing.
I don't want to hear it.
So that's how you really are?
If she can't fill the bottle, her wish won't come true.
Ginsei!
So without it...
Stop!
I don't feel like taking orders from you anymore.
Ginsei!
Please!
Give back that bottle!
Without it, Kobato will...
Please.
Ever since he's been with that girl, he's been a little weird.
"Please"?
The old you never would have said that.
Hurry and get it over with.
Ginsei...
Ioryogi!
Kobato?
Kohaku!
What's wrong?
I can't find Ioryogi!
He was in Sakura Park...
Come on! Catch me if you can!
Why you--!
He was having fun chasing one of his friends from the spirit world around, so I didn't stop and say hi.
Sakura Park, huh? Thank you.
You're welcome.
Damn it, this body's useless!
But if I've come this far...
That hurts, you asshole!
Ioryogi!
Where are you, Ioryogi?
Hey!
Fujimoto!
Here.
Ioryogi!
You're back!
Thanks for finding him!
I thought he was gonna become a stray.
A stray?
I'm so glad he's safe.
You care that much about it?
Yes! We're always together!
Tasty!
That bear always knows just what's needed!
It suits you so well.
You--
Ioryogi...
Thanks so much for getting the bottle back.
I really appreciate it.
Dobato! Minus 200 points!
What are you doing losing your precious bottle!? You don't deserve any more!
I'm sorry.
What is this, Fancy Day?
Everyone's wrapping me up!
We're always together!
Ioryogi.
What?
Ribbons really do suit you.
They don't!
You're wrong! Another one would be even better...
Stop it!
And another...
Hey! I told you to stop!
And one more.
I can't even talk...
People all want to fly
but they're cheated by gravity
everyone can really fly
She must be so unhappy because
she forgot her own shadow somewhere
Then...
If you tell me "thanks", if you say "thanks" and smile
Going back and forth, we'll be happy
You'll be happy, there'll be nothing to worry about
As long as we're together
It's strange, I'm crying even though I'm happy
...Angel and Guardian.
Next episode